<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Recommended Products &#8211; Smartika Shop</title>
	<atom:link href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product-category/recommended-products/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke</link>
	<description>Shop Smartika Today</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 07:35:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.10</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/Webp.net-resizeimage-150x60.png</url>
	<title>Recommended Products &#8211; Smartika Shop</title>
	<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>FERTILITY CLEANSE FOR WEMEN</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 15:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1238</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Fertility Cleanse For Women Performing a Fertility Cleanse is one of the best first steps you can take in preparation for conception and to support normal hormonal balance. How to Fertility Cleanse Naturally Doing a fertility cleanse is one of the best ways to boost your fertility and prepare for pregnancy, even if you have &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">FERTILITY CLEANSE FOR WEMEN</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/">FERTILITY CLEANSE FOR WEMEN</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1238" class="elementor elementor-1238" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="37e25de2" class="elementor-element elementor-element-37e25de2 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="252083e6" class="elementor-element elementor-element-252083e6 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="59658b38" class="elementor-element elementor-element-59658b38 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><strong>Fertility Cleanse For Women
</strong>
Performing a Fertility Cleanse is one of the best first steps you can take
in preparation for conception and to support normal hormonal balance.

<strong>How to Fertility Cleanse Naturally</strong>
Doing a fertility cleanse is one of the best ways to boost your fertility and
prepare for pregnancy, even if you have no fertility issues. If you are having difficulties getting pregnant though, you need to consider doing a fertility cleanse even more.

Cleansing is a simple, but super effective natural method to release toxins
from your body that are affecting your fertility.
The <strong>Fertility Cleanse</strong> supports the body’s own detoxification abilities to
help you achieve optimal reproductive wellness. The <strong>Fertility Cleanse</strong>
focuses on assisting the body’s natural ability to remove excess
hormones, support the uterus and promote normal liver function.

<strong>Fertility Cleanse</strong> for Woman has been formulated to the highest
therapeutic standards and manufactured under strict pharmaceutical
conditions to support <strong>Female sexual health and virility.</strong> This herbal
remedy has been used for many years to promote health and systemic
balance in the <strong>Female reproductive system.</strong>

During your lifetime you have undoubtedly been exposed to numerous
chemicals, such as:
Hormones present in non-organically raised meat, milk, and eggs.
Pesticides present in non-organically grown fruits and vegetables.
<b></b>
<ul>
 	<li>Use of plastic containers to store food and water.</li>
 	<li>Use of microwave ovens.</li>
 	<li>Household cleaning products.</li>
 	<li>Heavy metals like mercury present in dental 􀃗llings, certain type of 􀃗sh, and
even cosmetics.</li>
 	<li>Pollutants in the environment, especially if you live in a large city.</li>
 	<li>Smoke, alcohol, prescription medications and other substances.</li>
 	<li>Use of birth control pill and synthetic hormones.</li>
 	<li>Immunization containing thymerosal, a mercury derivative, aluminum and
other toxic adjuvants.</li>
</ul>
<strong>What will Fertility Cleanse Do?</strong>
Fertility <strong>Cleanse</strong> for women is a 100% natural, herbal remedy containing a
selection of herbs that support the <strong>health of the Female reproductive system.</strong>
We are exposed to environmental toxins each day. Excess toxins that our
bodies cannot filter which stored in our body, that is why regular internal
cleansing is recommended for optimal health.
Fertility Cleanse Pack contains products which helps remove stored toxins
from the body and helps body feel lighter and more energized.

The Fertility <strong>Cleanse</strong> for women focuses on assisting the body’s natural ability
to remove excess hormones, support the uterus and promote normal liver
function.

<strong>Benefits:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Supports the liver in detoxification of excess hormones and toxins</li>
 	<li>Assists the uterus in cleansing out old blood</li>
 	<li>Reduces occasional reproductive system discomfort</li>
 	<li>Promotes normal circulation to the reproductive system for optimal health</li>
 	<li>Works with the menstrual cycle for optimal cleansing</li>
</ul>
<strong>How the cleanse works:</strong>
The herbal formulas in the cleanse support the body’s natural ability to release
toxins by:

<strong>Encourages Normal Liver Function </strong><strong>–</strong> The liver is the filtering organ for the body, including hormones. The herbs in the Fertility Cleanse assist the liver’s natural ability to remove excess estrogen from the body.

<strong>Supports Uterine Health –</strong> In some instances the uterus is not able to empty
it’s entire contents every menstrual cycle. Some imbalances that show up
when this is happening are PMS, cramps during your period, brown blood/dark
blood/purple blood during menstruation, blood clotting during menstruation,
absence of menstruation, long cycles (longer than normal), or bleeding less
than 4 days per cycle. The herbs in the Fertility Cleanse support the uterus’s
ability to perform it’s natural monthly cycle.

<strong>Promotes Normal Uterine Circulation –</strong> Proper circulation is beneficial for
normal uterine health and hormonal balance. With proper circulation the
communication loop between the uterus and ovaries with the endocrine
system is able to function normally. The herbs in the Fertility Cleanse promote
normal uterine circulation and supports hormonal balance.

<strong>Fertility Cleanse Kit for women</strong>
Fertility Cleanse pack are comprises of 2X Berry Nectar, Multi-
Maca , Vitolize for Women, Probiotics and Arctic Sea.
The Natural Health pack contains the following components State Below:

<strong>Fertility Cleanse kit Ingredients</strong>

<strong>2 – Bottles of Aloe Berry Nectar:</strong> It detoxifies
the entire body systems of toxins.It contains more than 200 nutritional
compounds.This is a general body tonic that replenishes lost vital nutrients.
The berry nectar is Good for Female Reproductive System – Aloe Vera tonic is
wonderful for the female reproductive system. It helps to rejuvenate the
uterus. It is very beneficial to drink Aloe Vera gel if you are experiencing
painful menstrual cycle. Aloe Vera gel regularly replenishes the amino acid
de􀃗ciency in your body. The high vitamin content in it boosts up your body’s
immune system and self-defense mechanism.
<ul>
 	<li>2 of 2,000 ml of Aloe Berry Nectar Drink (8oz.)</li>
 	<li>1 x Bottle of Multi-Maca (60 tablet.)</li>
 	<li>1 x Pack of Probiotics (30 tablet.)</li>
 	<li>1 x bottle of Vitolize for Women (120 tablet.)</li>
</ul>
This kit will last 30 days (some products may last longer)
Fertility Cleansing Herbs
Fertility cleansing is best done using whole herbs as they are the safest way to
encourage cleansing in the body. Below are some of the herbs used in Fertility
Cleanse pack.
Female Fertility Cleanse pack Comprises of 6 Natural Nutritional
Supplement:
Fertility Cleanse for women is a Natural Fertility Health pack and it contains
the following components:

Multi-Maca
1 – Multi-Maca supplements, Multi Maca is an highly nutritious edible root,
which is a member of the radish family, helps promote the release of egg from
the ovary and helps to keep the female reproductive organs in good shape and
order making it very receptive to sperm cells. it Helps to overcome depression
&amp; chronic fatigue, Balances hormones, Helps 􀃗ght menopause symptoms,
Corrects menstrual irregularity / PMS issues, Increases and enhances libido.

<strong>Benefits for Women</strong>

Maca is used to correct hormonal imbalances in women which are responsible
for symptoms of PMS/PMT and menopause such as abdominal cramps, acne,
low blood sugar (cravings), hot 􀃘ashes, and depression (from low estrogen).
Because maca stimulates your body to produce the right quantities of
hormones, you can be less reliant on hormone pills or injections which can
have long-term negative effects.

Because modern women often juggle work, children, and housework for years
on end, fatigue is a common problem that seriously detracts from productivity
and enjoyment of life. Maca can help by improving your stamina and ability to
cope with stress.

For couples trying to have a baby, chances of conception may be improved
when both partners use Maca. Not only can maca increase sperm count and
potency, it can suppress ailments of the female reproductive system such as
ovarian cysts and urinary tract infections, and prolong the life-phase of
fertility. (Consult your doctor if you are receiving fertility treatments.)

60 tablets of Multi-Maca supplements is needed for 30 days,

<strong>Vitolize for Women</strong>
Vitolize for Women, an highly effective herbal blend which include vitamins,
minerals, and antioxidants to help preserve regular urinary 􀃘ow, support
optimal reproductive health and maintain healthy uterine function.
<strong>WOMEN’S VITALITY SUPPLEMENT</strong>

The <strong>INGREDIENT OF VITOLIZE WOMEN’S VITALITY SUPPLEMENT</strong>

(1) A proprietary blend of botanicals including, apple powder, passion-􀃘ower
and schizandra berry, all of which have been used in traditional herbal
medicine.
(2) Cranberry fruit powder that is made through a proprietary process that
intensifies the natural benefits of the whole cranberry, thereby delivering the
nutrients to the lower gastrointestinal tract where they can be absorbed
through a time-released mechanism.

(3) Magnesium, vitamin C and the B vitamins to support essential hormone
production.

(4) Iron and calcium, two critical minerals for women’s cardiovascular and
bone health. Natural blend of antioxidant-rich fruits, herbs, and vitamins and
minerals in Vitolize Women’s Vitality Supplement is speci􀃗cally designed with
a woman’s health needs in mind. Uncomfortable symptoms due to PMS and/or
menopause are related to hormone changes and speci􀃗c nutritional needs.

<strong>Vitolize Women’s Vitality Supplement</strong>
Vitolize for women aims to prevent the unwanted
symptoms and effects associated with hormonal issues and menopause.
Vitolize for women is a great way to improve your overall feminine health,
putting an end to irritating issues which can affect the female body in later life.

<strong>PRIMARY HEALTH BENEFITS OF VITOLIZE WOMEN’S VITALITY</strong>
<strong>SUPPLEMENT</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>promotes urinary tract health</li>
 	<li>supports healthy reproductive organs</li>
 	<li>provides nutritional support for hormonal balance</li>
 	<li>helps protect against free radical damage</li>
 	<li>Vitolize for Women’s promotes a balanced mood</li>
 	<li>Boost fertility rate in women</li>
 	<li>Fights ageing</li>
 	<li>120 tablets of Vitolize for Women is needed for 30 days.</li>
</ul>
<strong>Active Probiotic</strong>
<strong>1 – Active Probiotic:</strong> Unwanted bacterial strains and yeast can affect a woman’s
ability to have a baby, whether couples are trying the old fashioned way or through IVF.
Not only do these undesirable microbes negatively impact sperm, they can also make a
woman’s body less hospitable to her newly conceived child. Balancing the gut
microbiome helps crowd out harmful microbes throughout the body, including those
that may impact fertility.

Forever Active Probiotic helps in lowering the amount of
“bad” bacteria in your reproductive system that have or can cause infections
and other problems. It also helps balance your “good” and “bad” bacteria to
keep your body working like it should.
is the only shelf-stable, 6-strain probiotic on the
market today that requires no refrigeration. And what’s great about Forever
Active Probiotic is that it works in tandem with our patented aloe vera. Aloe
acts as a “prebiotic,” which fosters the growth of and provides the ideal
environment for the probiotic to function. So whether your goal is to promote
a healthy digestive system or enhance nutrient absorption and immune
function, add Forever Active Probiotic to your daily supplement program.

Forever Active Probiotic Helps Introduce probiotics directly to the vaginal
area and helps women showed promising results also improved the chances of
successful reproduction.
<ul>
 	<li>Promotes a healthy digestive system</li>
 	<li>Enhances nutrient absorption and immune function</li>
 	<li>Unique combination of 6 beneficial strains of microbes</li>
 	<li>No refrigeration needed</li>
 	<li>Show potential for supporting healthy fertility</li>
 	<li>Show to kept aging reproductive organs healthy</li>
</ul>
30 tablets of Probiotics is needed for 30 days.

The Fertility Cleanse supports the body’s own detoxification abilities to help you
achieve optimal reproductive wellness. The Fertility Cleanse focuses on assisting the
body’s natural ability to remove excess hormones, support the uterus and promote
normal liver function.

Fertility Cleanse for Woman has been formulated to the highest therapeutic
standards and manufactured under strict pharmaceutical conditions to support
Female sexual health and virility. This herbal remedy has been used for many years to
promote health and systemic balance in the Female reproductive system.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="4942486" class="elementor-element elementor-element-4942486 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="9cb2dcd" class="elementor-element elementor-element-9cb2dcd elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="b664b2a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-b664b2a animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/">FERTILITY CLEANSE FOR WEMEN</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fertility-cleanse-for-wemen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fibrofit Natural Therapy Pack</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 14:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1231</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>FibroFit Natural Therapy contains powerful organic herbal blend with enzymesdesigned to shrink single and multiple uterine Fibroids, reduce excess estrogen andsymptoms of Fibroids including heavy bleeding, blood clotting, cramping, pains, excesstissues, increase circulation to the reproductive organs and enhance chances of conception. Can be taken by women of all ages even after menopause, Prevents and shrink &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Fibrofit Natural Therapy Pack</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/">Fibrofit Natural Therapy Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1231" class="elementor elementor-1231" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="3b4597c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-3b4597c elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="7a77494a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-7a77494a elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="464e797e" class="elementor-element elementor-element-464e797e animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><p>FibroFit Natural Therapy contains powerful organic herbal blend with enzymes<br />designed to shrink single and multiple uterine Fibroids, reduce excess estrogen and<br />symptoms of Fibroids including heavy bleeding, blood clotting, cramping, pains, excess<br />tissues, increase circulation to the reproductive organs and enhance chances of conception. Can be taken by women of all ages even after menopause, Prevents and shrink Fibroids.</p><p>Natural herbal remedy to shrink uterine Fibroid tumors, products combination in Fibro<br />Fit remover pack is designed to shrink Fibroid s, and reduce the symptoms of 􀃗broid s,<br />including heavy bleeding, cramps, pain and pressure.</p><p><strong>FibroFit Natural Therapy</strong> is a 100% natural, herbal remedy containing a selection of<br />herbs that helps shrink uterine 􀃗broid tumors in Female reproductive system.</p><p><strong>FibroFit Natural Therapy</strong> has been formulated to the highest therapeutic<br />standards and manufactured under strict pharmaceutical conditions to help cure<br />Fibroid. This herbal remedy has been used for many years to promote health and<br />systemic balance in the female reproductive system.</p><p><strong>FibroFit Natural Therapy</strong> is a comprises of products to shrinks Uterine Fibroid s as it<br />help solves the root causes. FibroFit Natural Therapy is natural and it can be taken for<br />a two or three month with sensible diet and healthy lifestyle it will help shrinks the<br />Fibroids with no Negative side effect. These therapy are blend of nutritional natural<br />supplements and helps in improving and focusing solely on the overall reproductive<br />system and well being.</p><h2><strong>Here Are Few of The Benefits You Will Gain By Using The FibroFit</strong><br /><strong>Natural Therapy.</strong></h2><p>All product in Fibro Fit Natural Therapy tackles the internal cause of Uterine Fibroids<br />and fixes it permanently. By tackling all Fibroid contributing factors using a holistic,<br />multi dimensional approach it ensures the permanent eradication of the Uterine<br />Fibroid s internal environment. Here are few of the benefits our customers have<br />enjoyed after following the Fibroids Miracle program…</p><ul><li>Eliminate all types and sizes of Fibroids, naturally and safely</li><li>Prevent heavy periods, bleeding, cramping and clotting permanently</li><li>Eliminate the pain and bloating associated with Uterine Fibroids</li><li>Get rid of excessive weight</li><li>Become more relaxed and enjoy excellent sleep</li><li>Eliminate most digestive disorders</li><li>Feel lighter, healthier, look younger and more energetic.</li><li>Experience enhanced elimination, clockwork periods, thicker hair and healthier skin<br />and nails</li><li>Have increased mental clarity, enthusiasm and vitality.</li><li>Save 1000’s of Shillings and avoid the costs and consequences of surgery.</li></ul><h1>FibroFit Natural Therapy Testimonies</h1><div id="image_2052486670" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/fibrofit-testimonial-1.png" alt="" width="537" height="283" /></div></div><p><strong>Frequently Asked Questions</strong></p><p><strong>How Long Should I Take FibroFit Natural Therapy Before I See Results?</strong></p><p>We generally advise you to take it for 2-3 months before seeing the shrinkage in an<br />ultrasound scan, but many of our customers report feeling better after taking FibroFit<br />Natural Therapy after just 1 months!</p><p><strong>I Have Large Fibroids, will FibroFit Natural Therapy work for me?</strong></p><p>Yes! FibroFit Natural Therapy was formulated to help women with ALL sizes of<br />Fibroids. We have customers whose Fibroids are so large they resemble a 4-month<br />pregnancy. We have customers with numerous large Fibroids.</p><p>FibroFit Natural Therapy can help you regardless of the size of your Fibroids, but if you<br />have extra-large Fibroids, you will need to take it for longer before your Fibroids shrink<br />completely.</p><p><strong>What Are The Side Effects Of FibroFit Natural Therapy?</strong></p><p>FibroFit Natural Therapy contains only organic and non-sprayed ingredients, so there<br />are no negative side effects.<br />If you are on a short menstrual cycle, you may notice that adjusts itself to 28 days, but<br />we consider this to be a positive benefit!</p><p><strong>Does FibroFit Natural Therapy Really Work?</strong></p><p>Yes, FibroFit Natural Therapy really does work, and we have a very high success rate.<br />Most of our customers reorder this product because they are happy with the results<br />they get when they take FibroFit Natural Therapy.</p><p>FibroFit Natural Therapy has helped women of all ages (including post menopause)<br />and all races in many countries around the world.</p><p><strong>Can I Take FibroFit Natural Therapy If I Have Already Gone Through</strong><br /><strong>Menopause?</strong></p><p>Yes, FibroFit Natural Therapy is for women of all ages, and can help you shrink Fibroids<br />after menopause.</p><p><strong>Will FibroFit Natural Therapy Get Me Pregnant?</strong></p><p>We have found that Fibroids can disrupt implantation, or cause<br />miscarriages, which prevents a successful pregnancy. In these situations,<br />shrinking the Fibroids can help you have a healthy pregnancy.</p><p><strong>Can FibroFit Natural Therapy help me to lose weight?</strong></p><p>FibroFit Natural Therapy is not a weight loss remedy, as it focuses on shrinking<br />Fibroids, and managing the symptoms of Fibroids.</p><p>Many of our customers find that they lose inches around their abdominal area, and<br />shed pounds, but this is a result of Fibroid shrinkage.<br />FibroFit Natural Therapy does not help you lose weight around hips, thighs, arms etc.</p><p><strong>Can I take FibroFit Natural Therapy If I Am Pregnant?</strong></p><p>We don’t advise you to take any herbal remedies while pregnant. Not even FibroFit<br />Natural Therapy. However, we have a solution for pregnant women who want to stop<br />their Fibroids from growing and disrupting their pregnancy.</p><p><strong>How Do I Order FibroFit Natural Therapy?</strong></p><p>You can order FibroFit Natural Therapy online via our website, direct from Forever<br />company webstore, or via telephone and mobile payment.</p><p><strong>Do You Deliver To Any County?</strong></p><p>Yes, we deliver to all counties in Kenya.</p><p><strong>How Much Is Delivery?</strong></p><p>Delivery attract fixed costs of Kshs. 400 Standard G4S Rate when you order directly from<br />from our site with no extra charge</p><div id="image_45511376" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"> </div></div><p><strong>Note: Product is shipped in a discreet box,</strong><br /><strong>not the box pictured below.<br /><br /><br /></strong></p><p><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-1233" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-300x300.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="300" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-300x300.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-150x150.jpg 150w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-768x768.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-1024x1024.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-600x600.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17-100x100.jpg 100w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/products1_1_original-17.jpg 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" /></p><h2><strong>Fibro Fit Natural Therapy</strong><br /><strong>Combination Products Picture</strong></h2><div id="image_431662752" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"> </div></div><p><strong>FibroFit Natural Therapy</strong> comprises of <strong>Berry Nectar, Garlic thyme,</strong><br /><strong>Arctic Sea, Bee Propolis, Garcinia Plus, and Lycium plus.</strong> The<br />Nutritional natural supplements Health pack for Uterine Fibroid<br />s per unit contains and the following components State Below:</p><p><strong>FibroFit Natural Therapy Herbal Contains products below:</strong></p><p>2,000 ml of Berry Nectar Drink (8oz.)<br />1 Bottle of Garlic-thyme (100 tablet.)<br />1 Bottle of Lycium plus (100 tablet.)<br />1 Bottle of Garcinia plus (70 tablet.)<br />1 Bottle of Bee Propolis (60 tablet.)<br />1 Bottle of Bee Pollen (60 tablet.)</p><p>This kit will last for 30 days (some products may last longer).</p><p><strong>Berry Nectar:</strong></p><p>Your liver is constantly working to eliminate toxins, heavy<br />metals, bacteria and other impurities from the blood. We are exposed to<br />environmental toxins each day. Excess toxins that our bodies cannot 􀃗lter<br />which stored in our body, that is why regular internal cleansing is<br />recommended for optimal health.Excess hormones are also processed through<br />the liver. Proper liver health is essential to hormonal balance. Berry Nectar<br />helps for Urinary Tract and Liver Cleanser it also including vitamins, minerals,<br />enzymes, and amino acids that are essential for good health.</p><div id="image_721426458" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502716837546berry600-1.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502716837546berry600-1.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502716837546berry600-1-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502716837546berry600-1-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502716837546berry600-1-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits of Berry Nectar:</strong></p><ul><li>It protects the liver, it strengthens and repairs connective tissue</li><li>It supports the immune system and slows aging.</li><li>It aids rejuvenation</li><li>Detoxifies the entire body system of toxins (due to the presence of vitamin<br />A,C and E); protecting the cells, tissues and organs(strong antioxidant); aids<br />rejuvenation.</li><li>Cleanses the entire urinary tract system, prevents bacteria from adhering<br />to bladder cells. acidifies the urine… (help to combat candida, thrush and<br />other pid)… helpful against infections of the urinary tract</li><li>Also good for kidneys, bladder and skin… enhances their cleansing<br />functions.</li><li>Has anticancer properties</li></ul><p><strong>Garlic-thyme:</strong></p><p>Detoxifies the body and protects against infection by enhancing<br />immune function.<br />We humans are natural and natural therapy helps our health much better.<br />Study has shown its effectiveness against different strains of infection causing<br />microbes.</p><p>Studies have shown that garlic’s help the<br />metabolism convert fats to energy and protect the body against<br />free radicals. Other healthy substances in this odorless soft-gel It include<br />ajoene and lecithin, which can help emulsify fats. Garlic’s sulfur compounds<br />have also been shown to have beneficial properties.</p><div id="image_388411343" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>Rid the reproductive system of unhealthy growth.</li><li>Garlic-tyme, the two powerful antioxidant; combine to a great tool in<br />maintaining good health. it contains many sulphur compounds, which give it<br />its healing properties.</li><li>It is an ancient remedy for fighting against the growth of Fibroid tumor<br />because of it’s anti-inflammatory properties.</li><li>Disinfects the lungs and the skin; helps prevent body odor.<br />The odorless soft-gel capsule; helps support the conversion of fats to<br />energy due to lecithin.</li><li>Detoxifies the body and protects against infection by enhancing immune<br />function.</li><li>Lowers blood pressure and improves circulation.</li><li>Aids in the treatment of arteriosclerosis, arthritis, asthma, colds, and 􀃘u,<br />digestive problems, heart disorders, insomnia, liver disease, sinusitis , ulcers<br />by inhibiting growth of helicobacter pylori, the ulcer-causing bacterium.<br />good for virtually any disease or infection.</li><li>A great nutrient in the fight against cancer.</li></ul><p><strong>Dosage:</strong> Two tablets thrice daily before meal</p><p><strong>Forever Immublend:</strong></p><p>Forever ImmuBlend is used to correct hormonal imbalances in women which<br />are responsible for symptoms of PMS/PMT and menopause such as abdominal<br />cramps, acne, low blood sugar (cravings), hot flashes, and depression (from low<br />estrogen). Because Forever ImmuBlend stimulates your body to produce the<br />right quantities of hormones, you can be less reliant on hormone pills or<br />injections which can have long-term negative effects.The estrogen hormone<br />contributes to Fibroids by stimulating unwanted cell growth. Forever<br />ImmuBlend work to metabolize and get rid of excess estrogen, which in turn<br />helps to shrink uterine 􀃗broids.</p><p>Each ingredient in our proprietary blend is specifically chosen for the crucial<br />role it plays in supporting your body’s immune system function. It helps the<br />body’s biological defense system to operate at peak performance so you can<br />carry on your daily routine without any cares.</p><div id="image_1410569091" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>Supports all aspects of immune system function</li><li>Provides a variety of nutrients to support immune system activity<br />Fights free radicals</li><li>Helps to overcome depression &amp; chronic fatigue<br />Improves immune system: found to produce a “general sense of well-being”</li><li>Decreases stress and anxiety</li><li>Adjuvant to Hormone Replacement Therapy (HRT)<br />Corrects menstrual irregularity / PMS issues</li><li>Enhances fertility</li></ul><p>Our immune-enhancing nutrient blend includes the power of lactoferrin,<br />maitake and shiitake mushrooms, along with vitamins C &amp; D and zinc for that<br />extra boost. Each of these key ingredients contributes to your bodys wellbeing:</p><ul><li>Fructooligosaccharides – promote healthy levels of probiotic bacteria in the<br />digestive system.</li><li>Lactoferrin – supports immune cell production and helps maintain optimum<br />levels of beneficial bacteria in the intestines</li><li>Maitake &amp; Shiitake Mushrooms – support immune cell production and<br />cardiovascular function</li><li>Vitamin D – strengthens immune cells</li><li>Vitamin C – fights free radicals</li><li>Zinc – fights free radicals and supports immune cell production</li></ul><p><strong>Garcinia Cambogia Plus:</strong></p><p>Garcinia Cambogia Plus: This is an organic product that is made from<br />pumpkin like fruits that contains HCA(Hydroxycitric acid) a natural compound<br />which reduces the production of fat from carbohydrates. It also acts as a natural appetite suppressant.</p><div id="image_787535643" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-%C2%AB-Isolated.png" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated.png 900w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-768x768.png 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-600x600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="800" height="800" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>Helps rid the system off the unnatural growth.</li><li>It helps in starving the Fibroid because is a natural appetite suppressant.</li><li>Contains (HCA), hydroxycitric acid, a compound which reduces the<br />production of fats and the growth of 􀃗broid tumor.</li><li>Help Eliminate Extremely Damaging Toxins That Have Built Up Over the<br />Years</li><li>Destroy Harmful Parasites in Your Digestive Tract</li><li>Removes ‘Sludge’ From the Walls of the Stomach (that prevents Fat<br />Burning!)</li><li>Helps Get Rid of Gas and Bloating</li><li>Help Regulate Your Metabolism</li><li>We love the fact that the products are backed by a 100% satisfaction guarantee.</li></ul><p>DOSAGE: 2 tablet 3 times daily before meal, could be taken with meal if the<br />person is not fat.</p><p><strong>Lycium Plus:</strong></p><p>Lycium Plus: – a combination of Lycium and Licorice, contains over 150<br />bioactive phyto substances, including amino acids, polysaccharides, vitamins,<br />antioxidants… It strongly stimulates regenerative forces in the body, which is<br />seen in a slowing down of the aging process. It strengthens the organism ,<br />decreases fatigue, improves eyesight, prevents and removes side effects of<br />chemo and radiotherapy. Best results are achieved in combination with Aloe<br />Vera Gel, since Aloe, with its manifold action, enables complete absorption and<br />beneficial action of the natural substances of this preparative.</p><p>Lycium Plus supplement is easily absorbed and as it is natural, it has no<br />negative side effects.It is especially recommended in the following cases:</p><div id="image_668275193" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812513043lycium600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812513043lycium600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812513043lycium600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812513043lycium600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812513043lycium600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>Rid the reproductive system of unhealthy growth.</li><li>Regeneration of tissue and organs and slowing down the aging process.</li><li>Strengthening the organism and removing of fatigue.</li><li>Detoxification of organism, especially liver and kidneys.</li><li>Improving eyesight, especially removing of the so called night blindness.</li><li>Preventing and removing side effects of chemo and radiotherapy.</li><li>As a strong antioxidant to improve immune system.</li></ul><p><strong>DOSAGE:</strong> Two tablets thrice daily before meals</p><p><strong>Bee Propolis:</strong></p><p><strong>Bee Propolis:</strong> is is a bee hive product. Research has shown its effectiveness<br />against various of antibiotic microbes. Propolis contains 150 complex<br />compounds including many different bioflavonoids known<br />for their strong antimicrobial activities.</p><p>Bee propolis has been shown to be extremely anti-inflammatory which may<br />reduce endometriosis.</p><p>It appears more research on the benefits of bee propolis are in order. Because<br />preliminary studies suggest its highly anti-inflammatory properties it may be<br />greatly beneficial for fertility issues that may trigger inflammation response<br />such as uterine Fibroids, endometriosis, ovarian cysts, blocked fallopian tubes,<br />Pelvic Inflammatory Disease (PID), and reproductive trauma or surgeries.</p><p>Bee propolis may also contain immunomodulating properties. This may be<br />beneficial for autoimmune related fertility issues such as recurrent miscarriage due to immunological response (mothers body attacks and rejects the fetus), autoimmune related</p><p>Premature Ovarian Failure and antisperm antibody. Antisperm antibodies can<br />be present in woman as an allergic reaction to sperm, thus triggering immune<br />response to attack the sperm. These antisperm antibodies can also be present<br />in men as well, where their bodies attack their own sperm.</p><div id="image_1685254862" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273499111BEEPROPOLIS600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273499111BEEPROPOLIS600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273499111BEEPROPOLIS600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273499111BEEPROPOLIS600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273499111BEEPROPOLIS600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>Help to enhance the immune system, preventing Fibroids growth.</li><li>Fortified with Royal Jelly, contains Amino Acids, B-complex and Vitamins, a<br />super Food.</li><li>Natural and Powerful anti-Biotic, an Excellent Aid Against Bacterial, viral<br />Fungal infections.</li></ul><p><strong>DOSAGE:</strong> Two tablets thrice daily 1 hour before meals</p><p><strong>Bee pollen:</strong></p><p><strong>Bee pollen:</strong> Bee pollen is the food of the young bee and it is approximately 40%<br />protein. It is considered one of nature’s most completely nourishing foods. It<br />contains nearly all nutrients required by humans. About half of its protein is in<br />the form of free amino acids that are ready to be used directly by the body.It<br />can de-sensitize the body; good for allergy tolerance.</p><div id="image_103749651" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y"><div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div></div><p><strong>Benefits:</strong></p><ul><li>It aids in digestion and metabolism of fats, due to lecithin.</li><li>It improves the efficiency of the immune system and nervous system</li><li>Energy booster and for endurance, useful for combating fatigue.</li><li>Helps to correct body chemistry thereby prevent unhealthy growth;<br />counteract the effect of food additives and preservatives; useful in<br />combating colon disorders</li><li>Naturally high source of zinc and vitamin b6; beneficial for male fertility.</li><li>It has been called man’s complete food containing 22 amino acids,18<br />vitamins, 25 minerals, 59 trace elements, 11 enzymes, 14 fatty acids, 11<br />carbohydrates.</li></ul><p><strong>DOSAGE:</strong> Two tablets thrice daily 1 hour before meals</p></div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="11c274c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-11c274c elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="9218836" class="elementor-element elementor-element-9218836 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="8e1f27c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-8e1f27c animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/">Fibrofit Natural Therapy Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/fibrofit-natural-therapy-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diabetes Wellness Pack</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 14:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1226</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>THE 100% NATURAL SUPPLEMENT FOR DIABETES [*Diabetes Wellness Pack* ] Diabetes Wellness Pack is a pack of supplements that helps to lower the effect of diabetes and also help in reducing the blood sugar level in the system which helps to finally help you become diabetes free as you use them. Our nutritional supplement products &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Diabetes Wellness Pack</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/">Diabetes Wellness Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1226" class="elementor elementor-1226" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="1082ee34" class="elementor-element elementor-element-1082ee34 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="2d11bc8d" class="elementor-element elementor-element-2d11bc8d elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="689faa1c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-689faa1c animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><h2><strong>THE 100% NATURAL SUPPLEMENT</strong>
<strong>FOR DIABETES [*Diabetes Wellness Pack* ]</strong></h2>
Diabetes Wellness Pack is a pack of supplements that helps to lower the effect of
diabetes and also help in reducing the blood sugar level in the system which helps to
finally help you become diabetes free as you use them.

Our nutritional supplement products are made from the finest ingredients, grown or
collected from the best sources and produced with the most advanced technology.
Each product retains its original nutritional value, encouraging both good health and
peace of mind.

that have been in existence for over 5000 years, there is now a way by which you can
naturally lower your blood sugar level and 􀃗nally help you with reversing your diabetes

And best of all they are all natural supplement that will not give you any side effect like
what other medical drugs would give you.

How can you get access to this pack? But before I tell you how to get it. Let me tell you
the component of the pack
<h2><strong>THE 8 VITAL Diabetes wellness Pack HERBAL</strong>
<strong>SUPPLEMENTS</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Aloe Vera Gel:</strong></h3>
<div id="image_666849187" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg 512w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-150x150.jpg 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-300x300.jpg 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-100x100.jpg 100w" alt="" width="512" height="512" /></div>
</div>
This is a daily nutritional drink that helps to maintain the digestive system and also the
energy level in your body. It also helps in balancing the immune system. It has been
noted that the body cells becomes more sensitive to insulin when Aloe Vera gel
supplementation is regular. Good for detoxi􀃗cation or internal cleansing. may help
people with skin disorders, arthritis, asthma, bowel dysfunction, cramps, colon
cleansing, candida, diabetes, digestive disorder, herpes, headaches, heartburn,
hypertension, hemorrhoids, insomnia, indigestion, overweight, rashes, shingles,
stomach disorder, tiredness, tension, throat infection and ulcers.

Aloe has also been linked with:
<ul>
 	<li>Decreased blood lipids (fats) in patients with abnormally high levels of these
molecules in the blood (e.g. some people with ) and/or acute hepatitis (liver disease)</li>
 	<li>Decreased swelling and faster healing of wound injuries. Leg wounds and ulcers are
common complications of diabetes, and they typically take longer time to heal than
in healthy non-diabetic individuals.</li>
</ul>
These positive effects are thought to be due to the presence of compounds such as
lectins, mannans and anthraquinones.
<h2><strong>Garcinia Plus Capsules.</strong></h2>
<div id="image_1909995351" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-%C2%AB-Isolated.png" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated.png 900w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-768x768.png 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-600x600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440194237616Forever-Garcinia-Plus-«-Isolated-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="800" height="800" /></div>
</div>
The garcinia fruit extract and chromium content curbs appetite and breakdown fats
and carbohydrates. Garcina Plus – a natural dietary supplement from the fruit of the
garcinia cambogia tree. Contains chromium, lowers cholesterol and fatty acids,
enhances the liver’s ability to process calories more effectively, boosts metabolic rate.
it goes directly to the digestive tract through the liver reducing the need to eat
excessive amount of food ( an appetite suppressant)
<h2><strong>Forever Daily</strong></h2>
<div id="image_2038811854" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
<strong>The benefits of Forever Daily:</strong>

Forever Daily is a food supplement designed to deliver 100% of the recommended
daily allowance (RDA) of essential vitamins and bio-available minerals and nutrients.

Including Aloe Oligo Saccharide (AOS) complex, the most advanced nutrient delivery
system available, Forever Daily combines 55 perfectly balanced aloe coated nutrients
to support optimal health and vitality every day.

Forever Daily works to support daily energy needs, the immune system, proper
metabolism, cardiovascular health, bone health, and effective mental activity.

Forever Daily also contains FVX20, 20 specific fruit and vegetable extracts to
maximise the nutritional value offered by nature.

If taken alongside the Aloe Vera Gel, this synergy can increase the absorption of
certain nutrients by up to 3 times.

In essence, this product is synergistically balanced for optimum nutrition, providing a
balance of the crucial nutrients our bodies need when we are often neglecting them.
<h2><strong>ImmuBlend:</strong></h2>
<div id="image_1538663475" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Diabetes affects the metabolism as well as the immune system. The disease causes the
immune system to destroy insulin producing cells within the pancreas. The immune
response is also much lower in people who have diabetes so they are more susceptible
to getting infections that could result in the loss of a limb. ImmuBlend is designed to
support immune system function by addressing all aspects of the immune system from
its first line of defense to its last.

This exclusive formula addresses all aspects of immune system function, providing
both foundational nutrients required for a healthy immune system and natural
botanical that work synergistically to support immune function.
<h2><strong>Nature Min </strong></h2>
<div id="image_95292765" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895618716naturemin600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895618716naturemin600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895618716naturemin600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895618716naturemin600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895618716naturemin600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
advanced multi-mineral formula sourced from the sea bed. Include vital nutrients such
as chromium and selenium for maximum absorption of the body. it helps strengthen
bones and teeth; excellent source of trace minerals needed by the body, antidote for
myalgic encephalomyelitis ( Chronic Fatigue Syndrome), Osteoporosis, Candida
Muscle Cramps
<h2><strong>Ginkgo Plus:</strong></h2>
<div id="image_181932852" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
People with diabetes, if high blood glucose levels are experienced over a period of
years, our blood vessels can become damaged which can lead to poor Blood circulation
to neighboring cells due to high cholesterol accumulation in the arteries which prevent
poor blood circulation and rendering the body from delivering a sufficient amount of blood to the entire body system.

Ginkgo Plus Helps improve circulation and stimulate
the production of insulin in the body and allowing individuals to once again start
producing it. It Also helps in Various other Disorders. ginkgo plus helps diabetic issues
associated nerve damages and poor circulation, allergic reactions, vertigo, short-term
memory loss, migraine, atherosclerosis, ringing in the ears, cochlear hearing problems,
macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, and PMS
<h2><strong>Forever Gin Chia</strong></h2>
<div id="image_583063941" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811912024ginchia600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811912024ginchia600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811912024ginchia600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811912024ginchia600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811912024ginchia600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Forever Gin Chia Tablet is used for Anti-diabetic, Fatigue, Diabetes, Digestion,
Cardiovascular health, Tissue repair, Heart attack, Loss of appetite, Scurvy, Infection of
the intestine and other conditions. Forever Gin Chia Tablet may also be used for
purposes not listed in this medication guide.
Forever Gin Chia Tablet contains Calcium, Gingseng, Panax Ginseng, Salvia
Columbariae, Siberian Gingseng and Vitamin C as active ingredients.
Forever Gin Chia Tablet works by blocking the damage caused by free radicals thus
heals wounds; curing weakening of bones and for better absorption; restoring and
enhancing the normal well-being; improving psychological and immunal functions;
normalising blood glucose levels; decreasing cholesterol levels; reducing the appetite
in obese patients; possessing antidiabetic potential due to its ginsenoside component;
contributing towards metabolic activities due to ginsenosides components; increasing
the fat utilisation of the body; producing the action due to tanshinones content;
<h2><strong>Forever Gin Chia Tablet Working, Mechanism of</strong>
<strong>Action and Pharmacology</strong></h2>
Forever Gin Chia Tablet improves the patient’s condition by performing the following
functions:
<ul>
 	<li>Blocking the damage caused by free radicals thus heals wounds.</li>
 	<li>Curing weakening of bones and for better absorption.</li>
 	<li>Restoring and enhancing the normal well-being.</li>
 	<li>Improving psychological and immunal functions; normalising blood glucose levels;
decreasing cholesterol levels; reducing the appetite in obese patients; possessing antidiabetic potential due to its ginsenoside component; contributing towards
metabolic activities due to ginsenosides components.</li>
 	<li>Increasing the fat utilisation of the body.</li>
 	<li>Producing the action due to tanshinones content.</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Fields of Greens:</strong></h2>
With today’s busy lifestyles, and convenience of fast food, we all too often neglect
fresh, green foods. This Natural supplement is so powerful as it contains Chromium
Piconilate which is very very essential and necessary for glucose metabolism as it helps
with insulin efficiency and uptake by the body cells.
<h2><strong>Ellen Todd Diabetes and Nerve Issues FLP Testimony</strong></h2>
<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KzWoVAQmBwY" width="440" height="260" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe>

Ellen Todd discusses her struggle with diabetes and nerve damage and how Forever
Living Products allowed her body to heal itself.
<h2><strong>Watch Real Life Testimony by Steve Hart Who has
Heart Transplant and Diabetic.</strong></h2>
<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/KV-NqxyrcK0" width="440" height="260" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-mce-fragment="1"></iframe>

Amazing testimony by Steve Hart who had a heart transplant in 2002 and also he is a
diabetic since 2000. Find out which products he used to support his immune system
and how he managed to reduce his insulin intake by 38%, improved his blood work by
simply using Forever Living Products.

Using the combination inside the Diabetes Wellness Pack, you will notice changes in
your blood sugar level which help reduce the effect of being diabetic…

As you start to use it, you will start noticing changes in your body system and you will
also be astonished at how far you would have gone in helping to rid yourself of
diabetes.

And overtime, you will literally have to stop taking those medications as this natural
supplement will be performing way better than the industrial chemically produced
synthetic drugs. This supplement has no side effect.

The product has the prestigious Kosher Seal (which makes it acceptable to the Jews.
The Jews don’t take anything that isn’t 100% natural. Infact, they don’t even take bread
with yeast! They believe in no additives.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="130da54" class="elementor-element elementor-element-130da54 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="b8171f6" class="elementor-element elementor-element-b8171f6 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="1b5263f" class="elementor-element elementor-element-1b5263f animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/">Diabetes Wellness Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/diabetes-wellness-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>SMARTER KIDS PACK</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/smarter-kids-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/smarter-kids-pack/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 14:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1221</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The benefits may include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Improved thinking</li>
<li>Improved memory</li>
<li>Better social behavior</li>
<li>Better ability to perform everyday task</li>
</ul>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/smarter-kids-pack/">SMARTER KIDS PACK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1221" class="elementor elementor-1221" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="55e3ded" class="elementor-element elementor-element-55e3ded elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="72a3fbcd" class="elementor-element elementor-element-72a3fbcd elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="455be3f7" class="elementor-element elementor-element-455be3f7 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><h3><strong>Smarter Kids Care Memory Boost – Brain Booster Memory</strong>
<strong>supplement for Sharper Kids Focus, Better Recall, Faster Learning,</strong>
<strong>Improved Memory. Feel Younger and Experience Better Cognitive</strong>
<strong>Function</strong></h3>
Smarter Kids Care (Child brain Booster) SUPPORT CLEAR THINKING AND
OVERALL MIND POWER. Smarter Kids pack (kids Brain Booster) Focus functions as
a powerful brain booster to increase Kids memory strength, improve overall mood, and
boost neuro clarity by providing them with appropriate nutrients to enhance
concentration and health. The brain is a powerful muscle whose capabilities are limitless. Our herbal formula combination supports boosting your Kids brain power so
the may benefit from its full potential.

REDUCE CHILDREN SYMPTOMS OF AN OVERACTIVE MIND. Our natural
supplement can reduce overwhelming emotions or distractions that may hinder Kids
mental performance as an adult. Our formula provides the essential nutrients needed
to enhance positive brain activity, while relieving tension that can be caused by stress
or anxiety to the Kids.

STRONGEST SUPPLEMENT TO ENHANCE NEURO CLARITY.

<strong>Smarter Kids pack</strong>
<strong>(kids Brain Booster)</strong> combination has been shown to boost communication of positive
neurotransmitters while Ginkgo Biloba Leaf Extract is known to improve brain power
by increasing proper cellular circulation. Arctic Sea helps you feel more motivated and
focused by naturally boosting your energy levels. Our all-natural brain booster
includes <strong>Forever Bit n peaches</strong>, <strong>Arctic Sea,</strong> <strong>Ginkgo Plus and Forever Kids</strong> Combined
to further increase your chances of <strong>Kids</strong> clarity.

SAFE ALTERNATIVE TO INCREASE CHILD SHARPENED MENTALITY.
Optimal
Memory Focus is a natural and nutritional mood enhancer that is non-habit forming
and safe. It’s ideal for men and female who want to avoid dangerous prescription pills.
Take advantage of our superior brain activating vitamins to boost your mental focus
and memory. Our <strong>Smarter Kids pack (kids Brain Booster)</strong> combination will give you
real results – SIDE EFFECT FREE!

With the new school year in full swing, that means homework, assignments and tests
are back on the agenda. While eating right, adequate sleep, play time and exercise are
all critical to your child’s academic success, there are a few extra things we can
consider to support their cognitive health to make this school year a “gold star” year.

Brain development begins within a week of conception and by five weeks after
conception, the cells in begin dividing rapidly to form the 100 billion neurons (brain
cells) present at birth. By the age of four, the brain has increased to 80% of its adult
weight. Nutrition, including supplementation, plays a fundamental role in this rapid
development.

Children with attention-de􀃗cit disorder and learning disabilities who eat more
nutrient-dense foods learn, pay attention and behave better in school than those who eat more sweets, fried foods and salty foods. That’s the conclusion of an article
published in “Psychiatry Research” in 2012. Because nutrient de􀃗ciency affects
children’s brain function, reversing deficiencies can improve their memory and focus.
Incorporating nutrient-dense foods into your child’s diet is the best way to increase
her nutritional intake, but taking them as a supplement can be best for your children.
<h2><strong>Benefits of Smarter Kids pack:

</strong></h2>
When The kids take Natural products in Smarter Kids pack (kids Brain Booster), you
are at the same time allowing into your
-kids need good eyesight to see the blackboard in school and aim for the soccer goal.
That’s why vitamin A is so important help– especially for color and night vision.
<ul>
 	<li>It also gives their immune system an infection-fighting boost.</li>
 	<li>It boost mental Capacity of the child</li>
 	<li>It also allows stronger bone formation.</li>
 	<li>IMPROVED MEMORY- Experience greater memory consolidation</li>
 	<li>FASTER LEARNING- Improved clarity and comprehension</li>
 	<li>SHARPER FOCUS- Work harder and be more productive at home and at work</li>
 	<li></li>
 	<li>BETTER RECALL- Experience improved recall and fewer tip-of-your-tongue
moments</li>
</ul>
SIMPLE 30-DAY MONEY-BACK GUARANTEE- If you’re not satisfied with this
product get your money back hassle-free
<h2><strong>Below are The Powerful Brain Boosting Supplement to Help Boost</strong>
<strong>Children Brain Power

</strong></h2>
<h3><strong>Forever Kids</strong></h3>
<div id="image_1670643961" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811536037kids600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811536037kids600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811536037kids600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811536037kids600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811536037kids600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Forever Kids – [Chewable Multi-Vitamins]

Give your kids the nutrients they need each day with Forever Kids Chewable
Multivitamins. These fun and delicious, grape flavored multivitamins provide both
adults and growing kids ages two and older with the vital vitamins, minerals and
phytonutrients they may be lacking.

Formulated without artificial colors or preservatives, the phytonutrient base is taken
from such nutritious foods as carrots, beets, broccoli, spinach, blueberries, apples,
cranberries, tomatoes and strawberries. You and your kids will love the natural grape
flavor, and you’ll love the peace of mind!

*No artificial colors or preservatives


<strong>Benefits of Forever Living KIDS Multivitamin:</strong>

When you take Natural Forever Kids vitamin, you are at the same time allowing into
your or your children system many bene􀃗cial active healthy vitamins, nutritients like
Vitamin A, C, D3, E, B1, B2, B6, B12, Niacin, Folate (Folic acids), Calcium, Iron,
Magnesium, Zinc, Copper… ,which works their way into your body.

<strong>Vitamin A Benefits:

</strong>
–kids need good eyesight to see the blackboard in school and aim for the soccer goal.
That’s why vitamin A is so important — especially for color and night vision. It also
gives their immune system an infection-fighting boost.

Iron is a new addition to Forever Kids for its role in immune support and cognitive
development. Iron, a commonly deficient nutrient, also supports overall health.

Forever Kids Tablet improves the patient’s condition by performing the following
functions:
<ul>
 	<li>Facilitating retina formation required for low light and color vision.</li>
 	<li>Blocking the damage caused by free radicals thus heals wounds.</li>
 	<li>Increasing absorption of calcium and phosphorus required for strong bones.</li>
 	<li>Slowing down the processes that damage cells.</li>
 	<li>Metabolizing carbohydrate thus maintains normal growth.</li>
 	<li>Maintaining many tissues of the body to prevent vitamin B2 deficiency.</li>
 	<li>Producing antibodies and hemoglobin by keeping blood sugar level in normal range.</li>
 	<li>Maintaining fluid balance within body cells and acidity levels.</li>
 	<li>Improving and maintaining the immune function.</li>
</ul>
<h2><strong>Arctic Sea Omega 3

</strong></h2>
<div id="image_591686570" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
<ul>
 	<li>BOOST YOUR KIDS OMEGAS: If you’re like most parents, you simply cannot get
your kids to eat enough fruits and vegetables with omegas. Now you can take one
serving of Omega3 DHA for KIDS, and get them the nutrition they need to be in
order to stay healthy.</li>
 	<li>GET TO OPTIMAL HEALTH: According to food nutrition, your kids needs such a
wide range of fruits, veggies, vitamins, minerals, natural fibers, enzymes, omegas
and probiotics in order to grow and be healthy, it’s no wonder you can’t give it
everything in the course of their daily diet. Now they can get all the omegas &amp; DHA
needed to keep their brains healthy and growing.</li>
</ul>
Powerful ingredients of Forever Arctic Sea (Omega 3 fatty acids) Will improve your
kids Digestive Function, making Food … to provide them with the correct balance of
Omega 3 fatty acids, which can boost children heart function, brain function and
eyesight.

Omega-3 fatty acids are a healthy type of fat required in brain cell membranes. The
body cannot synthesize omega-3 itself, so it must be incorporated into your children
diet. When children are de􀃗cient in omega-3 fatty acids, it can affect their ability to
focus. Children with attention-deficit disorder are more likely to be deficient in omega-
3s, according to an article published in “Pediatrics” in 2012. The article also stated that
omega-3 supplements may benefit children with attention-deficit disorder who aren’t
seeing results from medication.
<h2><strong>Ginkgo Plus:

</strong></h2>
<div id="image_820290253" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812395906ginkgo600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Feed your Child mind with Ginkgo Biloba, the legendary “brain tonic” dating back 5000
years ago. Forever Ginkgo Plus is a unique blend of four Chinese plants. Ginkgo tree is
said to be the oldest surviving tree species.

They live incredibly long (often over 1,000years), and are extremely resistant to fungi
and insects. Ginkgo Biloba is one of the most popular herbal supplements available in
Europe and North America.

Extract from the ginkgo leaf yields flavonoids and terpenoids which strengthen
capillaries. They act also as antioxidants. Ginkgo has been shown to increase
circulation of the blood to the brain, making it a remarkable “brain tonic.” It also aids
with poor memory and mental fatigue, elevates mood and energy, and increases
concentration, alertness and metabolism

Ginkgo Plus – GiIncreases Concentration
Research shows that ginkgo can help combat poor concentration, reverse cognitive
decline and and heal fatigue. It’s even useful for helping to treat cerebral insuf􀃗ciency
— a condition characterized by chronically low concentration, confusion, decreased
physical performance, fatigue, headaches and mood changes.

Many of the brain-boosting ginkgo biloba benefits that researchers have discovered
rest on the fact that it’s an effective anti-inflammatory that increases antioxidant
activity, lowers oxidative stress and improves circulation — all important factors for
maintaining cognitive health.
<h3><strong>The benefits may include:

</strong></h3>
<ul>
 	<li>Improved thinking</li>
 	<li>Improved memory</li>
 	<li>Better social behavior</li>
 	<li>Better ability to perform everyday task</li>
 	<li>Food for the brain, enhance blood circulation in the brain.</li>
 	<li>Potent anti-oxidant, anti-aging, anti-stress and anti-depressant.</li>
 	<li>Reduces risk of Alzheimer’s disease.</li>
 	<li>Increases oxygen supply to the heart, brain and the entire body.</li>
 	<li>Normalizes blood sugar and blood pressure, inhibits blood clotting.</li>
 	<li>Improves memory and relieves muscle pains.</li>
 	<li>Helpful for vertigo, hearing loss, impotence, tinnitus, varicose veins, hemorrhoids.</li>
 	<li>Relieves leg cramps by improving circulation.</li>
 	<li>Effective for asthma, eczema, kidney disorders.</li>
 	<li>Helps in the treatment of fatigue, viral infections, tumor, cancer, migraine.</li>
 	<li>Prevents graying of hair (due to Fo-ti content).</li>
 	<li>Regulates the immune system</li>
</ul>
There are 2.2 billion children in the world, many are malnourished. New treatments
and remedies are introduced every day on the marketplace to help with the ailments
and conditions listed above

Many have benefited from taking Smarter Kids pack (kids Brain Booster) . It’s not
only for children. Adults can take products in Smarter Kids pack.

So, among st all the choices you make this year to help keep your kids healthy and
successful, consider a boost to help them continue building better brains and striving
for that “gold star

You Can Contact Us Now To place Your Order And We Will Deliver To You Any Where
Within The Country (Kenya) Within 24 hours.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="88ed71d" class="elementor-element elementor-element-88ed71d elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="81372bb" class="elementor-element elementor-element-81372bb elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="8bb969a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-8bb969a animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/smarter-kids-pack/">SMARTER KIDS PACK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/smarter-kids-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>High Blood pressure Natural</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 16:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1214</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Blood pressure is the force of blood against your artery walls as it circulates through your body. Blood pressure normally rises and falls throughout the day, but it can cause health problems if it stays high for a long time. Before I go ahead and talk about product recommend for blood pressure we should also &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">High Blood pressure Natural</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/">High Blood pressure Natural</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1214" class="elementor elementor-1214" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="2503eac8" class="elementor-element elementor-element-2503eac8 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="131526c1" class="elementor-element elementor-element-131526c1 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="419468d9" class="elementor-element elementor-element-419468d9 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Blood pressure is the force of blood against your artery walls as it circulates
through your body. Blood pressure normally rises and falls throughout the day,
but it can cause health problems if it stays high for a long time.

Before I go ahead and talk about product recommend for blood pressure we
should also know some basic about blood pressure itself in simple language.

When our heart beats, blood is pumped into the arteries. The force with which
the blood is pushed against arterial walls is called blood pressure.

The pressure is the highest when the blood is pumped during each heart beat
and is called systolic pressure. When the heart rests between each beat, the
blood pressure drops and is called diastolic pressure.

Blood pressure is high when these two readings is equal to or greater
than140/90. This is hypertension.

The issue with high blood pressure is that it is not a disease in itself, but if you
have high blood pressure you are a risk of having other serious problems. High
blood pressure will not display symptoms but could cause serious health
problems like heart attack, heart failure, stroke or kidney failure.

It can be controlled by adopting a healthy lifestyle and taking appropriate
medication. Low blood pressure (equal to or less than 120/80) could cause
dizziness or fainting spells. Some people can live normal lives with low blood pressure.
<div id="image_2067823013" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg 512w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-150x150.jpg 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-300x300.jpg 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-100x100.jpg 100w" alt="" width="512" height="512" /></div>
</div>
Powerful natural food supplements to help have a 􀃗nal solution and remedy to
High blood pressure and heart related health challenges. These supplements
from Forever Living Products are combined together to help you have a
sustainable and normal blood pressure. No Side Effect! All Natural Products.

These supplements, when combined with proper diet and exercise has been
known to help bring the blood pressure down to the normal level. And
continuous use ensures a healthy heart.

The supplements in the pack includes;

<strong>CardioHealth® with CoQ10</strong> and <strong>Aloe Vera Gel.</strong> This is special formula that
provides
<ul>
 	<li>Heart healthy antioxidants that protects the heart
Is necessary for the basic functioning of cells, including those of the heart
and blood vessels</li>
 	<li>promotes healthy homocystein level thus preventing heart attack
contains a selection of herbal extracts (Grape Seed, Turmeric, Boswellia,
and Olive Leaf) found in studies to be beneficial for cardiovascular support.</li>
 	<li>prevents hardening of arteries and supports a healthy heart and blood
vessel function</li>
 	<li>supplies minerals such as magnesium,chromium and lecithin which
lubricates the blood vessels and mobilizes fat thereby reducing blood
cholesterol</li>
 	<li>promotes efficient cell function and prevents weakness of the heart
prevents blood clot in the arteries and eases blood flow.</li>
 	<li>Garlic Thyme is a powerful antioxidant that helps to;
Lower blood pressure and improves circulation</li>
 	<li>prevents heart disorders</li>
 	<li>helps maintain a healthy cholesterol level in the bloodstream</li>
</ul>
<strong>Garlic Thyme</strong> is a powerful antioxidant that helps to;
<ul>
 	<li>Lower blood pressure and improves circulation</li>
 	<li>prevents heart disorders</li>
 	<li>helps maintain a healthy cholesterol level in the bloodstream</li>
</ul>
Arctic Sea is a combination of Omega-3 with Omega-9
<ul>
 	<li>beneficial against cardiovascular disease</li>
 	<li>Omega-3 and Omega-9 fatty acids can help support healthy cholesterol and
triglyceride levels</li>
 	<li>prevents and dissolves blood clots.</li>
</ul>
All these supplements work together for a healthier heart.

<strong>Below are the list of 6 recommend products that helps regulate blood</strong>
<strong>pressure.</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>2x Aloe Vera Gel</li>
 	<li>1x Arctic-Sea Omega-3</li>
 	<li>1x Garlic thyme</li>
 	<li>1x Forever cardiohealth</li>
 	<li>1x A-Beta Care</li>
</ul>
2 Aloe Vera Gel
<div id="image_214825810" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg 512w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-150x150.jpg 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-300x300.jpg 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-100x100.jpg 100w" alt="" width="512" height="512" /></div>
</div>
Aloe vera gel sweeps away these toxins and make the villi
function properly in absorbing the nutrients into the bloodstream.
This also makes Arctic Sea ef􀃗ciently absorbed into the bloodstream. There, it
dissolves the arterial plaque that accumulate in your arteries.The miraculous
aloe leaf has bene􀃗ted mankind for thousands of years. helps boost your
immune system. contains 200 nutritional compounds including 20 minerals
and 18 amino acids, 12 vitamins which provides all the bene􀃗ts what body
daily needed. Helps in detoxi􀃗cation and cleansing or the arteries, veins, blood
stream and the heart itself. Aloe vera also contains vitamins E, C, B12 and A.
Vitamin C in particular is good to help with blood circulation and helps
maintain normal functioning of blood vessels.

<strong>Here’s are the six aloe Vera benefits for your heart, based on the cited</strong>
<strong>research reports:</strong>
<ol>
 	<li>Lowers LDL cholesterol</li>
 	<li>Increases HDL cholesterol</li>
 	<li>Reduces triglycerides</li>
 	<li>Lowers blood pressure</li>
 	<li>Stabilizes heart rhythm</li>
 	<li>Reduces occurrence of chest pain (angina) attacks</li>
</ol>
<strong>Arctic-Sea Omega-3</strong>
<div id="image_504814521" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
I mentioned, Omega-3 rich in two substances (EPA and DHA), these are
important elements that help lowering the harmful cholesterol level and the
triglyceride as well decreasing the risk of artery blockage. Omega-3 fats
supports cardiovascular health by cleaning the arteries. Omega-3 is an
essential polyunsaturated fatty acid found in salmon and other cold-water
ocean fish. Omega-9 is the unsaturated fatty acid found in vegetable products.
It have been shown to support heart health, cognitive function, eye health,
healthy joints. Recommended by World health organization and American
Heart association in 2011 for consumption cause of Omega-3’s EPA and DHA
to help maintain heart health, hence affirming that Forever Arctic Sea Omega
3 can help keep you and your family heart healthy for years to come. you ca
read the Top 10 reason to take Forever New and Improved Arctic Sea Omega-
3 Fish Oil.

The strongest health benefit of omega-3 is related to
heart health. This includes helping to maintain a regular heart rhythm,

<img class="alignnonewp-image-693" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/bigstock-Atherosclerosis-55097483-e1416802915580-544x400.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 398px) 100vw, 398px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/bigstock-Atherosclerosis-55097483-e1416802915580-544x400.jpg 544w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/bigstock-Atherosclerosis-55097483-e1416802915580-600x441.jpg 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/bigstock-Atherosclerosis-55097483-e1416802915580.jpg 720w" alt="" width="398" height="293" />

reducing blood pressure, lowering blood fat levels and slowing down the rate
at which our arteries get clogged up. Besides these general health bene􀃗ts.
<ul>
 	<li>helps to regulate and normalize blood pressure (effective for hypertensive
cases). if it is down it will bring it up,and if is high
it will bring it to normal level.</li>
 	<li>Lowers cholesterol.
Relieves Migraine headaches.</li>
 	<li>Improves blood circulation, varicose veins, burning feet, prostrate
problems.</li>
 	<li>Helps to relieve symptoms of arthritis, widespread pain in the joints,
muscles and tendons, rheumatism, osteoporosis, and gout.</li>
 	<li>Beneficial for diabetic patients.
Very effective in treating Eczema and Psoriasis.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Garlic thyme</strong></h3>
<div id="image_2106614077" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811618201garlic600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Garlic and garlic supplements can help lower
blood pressure and relax smooth muscles. Research on the health bene􀃗ts of
garlic is finding more and more miraculous effects. Among them, garlic seems
to help thin the blood, prevent the blockage in blood vessels, and
therefore lower blood pressure.

our forever Garlic and thyme Two powerful antioxidants, combine to create a
great tool in maintaining good health and good circulatory system. Its a
powerful antioxidant, it helps in controlling of blood sugar, blood pressure and
cholesterol and also helps prevent heart disease. It strengthens the immune
system and fights fungal and bacterial infections. When taken regularly, it
stimulates the liver and improves metabolism. Garlic and thyme bene􀃗ts
health by facilitating the treatment of conditions like atherosclerosis, arthritis,
tuberculosis, bronchitis, pneumonia, insomnia, hypoglycemia, intestinal
worms, digestive disorders, bladder stones, allergies, and various other
diseases. Plus, it is works as a good detoxi􀃗er. Moreover, Garlic and thyme
helps cure sexual disorders

<img class="alignnonewp-image-694" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/maxresdefault-711x400.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 466px) 100vw, 466px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/maxresdefault-711x400.jpg 711w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/maxresdefault-768x432.jpg 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/maxresdefault-600x338.jpg 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/maxresdefault.jpg 1280w" alt="" width="466" height="262" />

The herb helps avoid hardening of
arteries and prevents colon cancer, stomach cancer and oesophageal cancer as
it contains natural antioxidants and compounds with anti cancer properties.

Garlic and thyme is beneficial in lowering blood pressure because it helps
dilate peripheral blood vessels. it helps dissolve accumulated phlegm.

Studies have shown that Garlic and thyme may help decrease platelet
aggregation, which helps the blood flow more easily, thus helps the blood
pressure. An epidemiological study done in Pakistan found that individuals
with healthy blood pressure levels had significant quantities of Garlic and
thyme in their diet. Due to its content of sulfur and other compounds, Garlic
and thyme displays a natural ability to help support the respiratory system.

Forever Garlic Thyme is used today by many herbalists in the United States
and throughout Europe. read more benefits about Garlic and Thyme
<h3><strong>Forever Absorbent-C®</strong></h3>
<div id="image_1565578675" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
When it comes to blood vessel-friendly nutrients, it’s hard to beat vitamin C. It
functions as an antioxidant, which means vitamin C can help protect your
heart, blood vessels and other tissues from damage caused by toxins called
free radicals. Vitamin C is also crucial for the formation of collagen, one of the
proteins that keeps your arterial and venal blood vessel walls strong. You need
just a small amount of vitamin C daily — 90 milligrams for men and 75
milligrams for women — and you each reach your goals by eating at least 􀃗ve
servings of fruits and veggies each day

Daily vitamin C has long been associated with good health. Science now
provides us with a whole list of bene􀃗ts derived from this most famous of all
vitamins:
<ul>
 	<li>It is a powerful antioxidant, forming part of the body’s defense system
against the harmful effects of free radicals.</li>
 	<li>It is a beneficial supplement for the skin, as it supports the formation of
intercellular collagen</li>
 	<li>It is necessary for the maintenance of healthy connective tissue.</li>
</ul>
Vitamin C is water soluble, and is secreted from the body. Since humans are
among the few animals that are unable to make their own vitamin C, we must
therefore get it from our food, drinks, and supplements, such as Forever
Absorbent-C®.

The need for adequate levels of vitamin C is very evident. Science reports that
one cigarette destroys 25mg of vitamin C. Stress, medication and
environmental factors all heavily deplete the body of this vitamin. A deficiency
can result in broken capillaries and bleeding gums.

Forever Absorbent-C® with Oat Bran is an outstanding nutritional
supplement. It combines two vital nutrients into one convenient product. The
bonded matrix composition, is a unique delivery system combining 500 mag of
oat bran with the full 60 mg of Vitamin C in each tablet.
<h3><strong>Forever CardioHealth® with CoQ10</strong></h3>
<div id="image_1122154603" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1493314111586CardioHEalth-StickPacks.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1493314111586CardioHEalth-StickPacks.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1493314111586CardioHEalth-StickPacks-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1493314111586CardioHEalth-StickPacks-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1493314111586CardioHEalth-StickPacks-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Coenzyme Q10, more commonly known as CoQ10, is an antioxidant critical
for supporting heart health. It’s crucial if you’ve ever been on blood pressure
or, in particular, cholesterol-lowering medication. Two-to-three hundred
milligrams of Coenzyme Q10 per day is a great, natural remedy for high blood
pressure.

Forever CardioHealth® with CoQ10 is a special formula designed to mix with
our Forever Aloe Vera Gel<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> to provide three important nutritional supports
for cardiovascular health.

Forever CardioHealth® supports healthy homocysteine levels, supplies coenzyme
Q10 to promote ef􀃗cient metabolism, and provides heart-healthy
antioxidants. Simply pour, stir and drink – it’s that easy – and your heart will
thank you!
<ul>
 	<li>Designed to mix with Forever Aloe Vera Gel<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/11/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></li>
 	<li>Provides CoQ10, necessary for basic cell functions</li>
 	<li>Contains heart-healthy herbal extracts, minerals, lecithin and antioxidant
vitamins</li>
</ul>
CoQ10 is an enzyme that is produced by the human body and is necessary for
the basic functioning of cells, including those of the heart and blood vessels.
CoQ10 levels are reported to decrease with age, which is just when we need them most. Forever CardioHealth® with CoQ10 provides the extra supply of
CoQ10 your body needs.
<h3><strong>CoQ10 Benefits</strong></h3>
<ul>
 	<li>It helps in biochemical reactions in your body that provides energy</li>
 	<li>It is essential in your body’s metabolism of fat and energy</li>
 	<li>It prevents the accumulation of fatty acids in the heart muscle</li>
 	<li>It is believed to help the remaining muscle cells function more ef􀃗ciently in
persons suffering from cardiomyopathy</li>
 	<li>Pretreatment with CoQ10 prevents oxidative damage after angioplasty or
bypass surgery</li>
</ul>
<strong>Why CoQ10 Supplements Are Good For Your Heart</strong>

Studies showed that CoQ10 supplementation improved the heart function in
persons with congestive heart disease.

Here’s why Forever CardioHealth with CoQ10 is one of the best CoQ10
supplements in the market today.
<h3><strong>Other recommended Product you may like to</strong>
<strong>add to help control high blood pressure</strong></h3>
<h3><strong>Forever Argi+</strong></h3>
<div id="image_510001686" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Argi+ helps to distribute nutrients from our food
throughout the body. This bene􀃗ts normal healthy people by getting their
good nutrition to the muscles, tissues and organs where it is needed, as well as
those that struggle with lack of energy.

Argi+ is the proprietary combination of L’Arginine put together by Forever
Nutraceuticals – part of the Forever Living Products organisation. Argi+
contains both L’Arginine and also a range of super fruits (eg. pomegranate, red
wine extract and grape skin which help support our bodily systems).

L-Arginine is an amino acid that’s so potent, that scientists have referred to it
as the “Miracle Molecule.”

And for good reason, because our bodies convert L-Arginine into nitric oxide, a
molecule that helps blood vessels relax and open wide for greater blood flow.
This can help anyone engaging in exercise but also those who struggle
with blood pressure issues.

Why is greater blood flow important?
Greater blood flow matters because it supports many key functions in our
body:
<ul>
 	<li>Healthy blood pressure levels</li>
 	<li>Overall cardiovascular health</li>
 	<li>Immune function</li>
 	<li>Muscle growth</li>
 	<li>Bone &amp; tissue growth &amp; repair</li>
 	<li>Male sexual function</li>
 	<li>Fat and glucose metabolism</li>
 	<li>Anti-aging hormone production and much more</li>
</ul>
And for sports people, they can perform better and recover faster.
<div id="image_1503949324" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"></div>
</div>
High Blood Pressure Natural Pack Blood pressure is the force of blood against your
artery walls as it circulates through your body. Blood pressure normally rises and falls
throughout the day, but it can cause health problems if it stays high for a long time.
Below are the list of 5 recommend products that helps regulate blood pressure.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="8967b47" class="elementor-element elementor-element-8967b47 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="3fcd606" class="elementor-element elementor-element-3fcd606 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="07788c8" class="elementor-element elementor-element-07788c8 animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/">High Blood pressure Natural</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/high-blood-pressure-natural/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Forever Arthritis Care Pack</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1205</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Forever Arthritis Care Pack is a complete joint care pack that work synergistically to help promote healthy joints. Especially useful for people who suffer from joint pain and those who want to prevent them, including athletes. As Our body ages, it is less able to produce the natural elements that make up healthy cartilage, the smooth &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Forever Arthritis Care Pack</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/">Forever Arthritis Care Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1205" class="elementor elementor-1205" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="6d10a614" class="elementor-element elementor-element-6d10a614 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="69ab822a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-69ab822a elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="783a03f2" class="elementor-element elementor-element-783a03f2 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Forever Arthritis Care Pack is a complete joint care pack that work synergistically to help promote healthy joints.
Especially useful for people who suffer from joint pain and those who want to prevent
them, including athletes.

As Our body ages, it is less able to produce the natural elements that make up healthy
cartilage, the smooth rubbery connective tissue on the end of bones.

All Products contained in Forever Joint Care Pack Together helps Repair damaged
tissue by regenerating cells is a function at which all product in Forever Joint Care has
been shown to be most successful. It not only relieves the painful symptoms but also
helps to disperse damaged tissue. Forever Joint Care Pack are to be taken both
internally and externally as a juice and supplement or as a gel applied to the painful
joint. Forever Joint Care Pack helps deep penetration to the joint.

<strong>FOREVER FREEDOM</strong>
<div id="image_44547580" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768.jpg 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768-280x280.jpg 280w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768-400x400.jpg 400w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768-300x300.jpg 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768-600x600.jpg 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/0196-forever-freedom-gel-estabilizador-aloe-vera-forever1-c53e8ff57bdaf482888cdb90f9a18d4c-1024-1024-768x768-100x100.jpg 100w" alt="" width="768" height="768" /></div>
</div>
Forever Freedom® has combined aloe vera with substances that are helpful
for the maintenance of proper joint function and mobility in a tasty, orange-
flavored juice formula.

We’ve taken Glucosamine Sulfate and Chondroitin Sulfate – two naturally
occurring elements that have been shown to help maintain healthy joint
function and mobility – and married them with our stabilized aloe vera gel. To
this, we’ve added vitamin C and MSM, a primary source of bio-available sulfur
the body needs to maintain healthy connective tissues and joint function.

Glucosamine Sulfate and Chondroitin Sulfate are natural substances that help
maintain the structure and health of cartilage, keeping this natural “shock
absorber” well hydrated. They also help keep the lubricating fluid within the
joint at the necessary viscosity to allow one surface to glide freely over
another. As the body ages, it is less able to produce these natural elements of
healthy cartilage which can then lead to “wear and tear” on the joints.
<ul>
 	<li>Combines 100% stabilized Aloe Vera with Glucosamine Sulfate,
Chondroitin Sulfate and MSM (Methyl sulfonyl methane) which are needed
for maintaining joint function and to quicken the healing of joints and
muscles.</li>
 	<li>It is enhanced with VitaminC and MSM provide essential elements for
maintaining connective tissue (including bones, joints, muscles and nails).</li>
 	<li>Helps to relieve joint and muscle in inflammation and pain.</li>
</ul>
<strong>FOREVER ARCTIC-SEA</strong>
<div id="image_735111073" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811434794articsea600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
<strong>Arctic Sea:</strong> Can help to improve blood circulation clean the arteries. When the
blood circulation is good, joint health will be improved as well. It also helps
in dissolving plaque on arteries and enable moving of all necessary Nutrition’s
to the appropriate bodies.

<strong>Benefits of Arctic sea</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Omega-3 fatty acids have been shown to help support circulatory function</li>
 	<li>Omega-3 and Omega-9 fatty acids can help support healthy cholesterol and
triglyceride levels.</li>
 	<li>It help to improve memory and concentration.</li>
 	<li>It help clean the heart and arteries.</li>
 	<li>It regulate blood pressure.</li>
 	<li>It help in strengthening the muscles.
Omega 3 polyunsaturated fatty acids are derived from cold water fish
that have anti-inflammatory properties. It also help to reduce body fats and
flush out excess estrogen that which contributes to Fibroids.</li>
 	<li>Omega 6 fatty acids are derived from calamari oil(a polyunsaturated
vegetable oil) is also effective against the shrinking of Fibroid</li>
 	<li>Rich in Omega 3 and Omega 9 (from olive oil) that have anti-in ammation
property that helps reduce pain.</li>
 	<li>With added Vitamin E that acts as antioxidant to the beneficial oils in the
soft-gels.</li>
</ul>
<ol>
 	<li>To cushion our body and protect our cells and organs.</li>
 	<li>To lubricate our joints for easy movement and freedom from arthritis.</li>
 	<li>To clean our veins and arteries for easy blood flow and many more benefits.</li>
</ol>
The FOREVER ARCTIC-SEA is not sold in any pharmacy shop. You can now
place your order direct from our website <a href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/arctic-sea/">here&gt;&gt;ORDER NOW&lt;&lt;</a>

&nbsp;

<strong>FOREVER ACTIVE HA</strong>
<div id="image_986956083" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812822413activeha600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812822413activeha600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812822413activeha600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812822413activeha600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502812822413activeha600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Forever Active HA® provides a unique form of low molecular weight
hyaluronic acid, with moisturizing and lubricating properties, plus Ginger Oil
and Turmeric – making it one of the most powerful nutritional joint and skin
moisturizing supplements on the market.

Hyaluronic Acid (HA) is a special protein that our bodies produce to lubricate
and cushion our joints and muscles, as well as to insure adequate skin
hydration. As we age, our bodies produce less and less HA. With less HA, our
joints can lose their natural lubrication, and our skin appears rough and dry.
Until recently, HA had to be injected because the digestive system could not
absorb it in its natural state; but thanks to a new and unique process, HA may now be consumed orally. And for centuries, Chinese herbalists have used
Ginger and Turmeric to help promote proper joint function.

With low molecular weight HA, plus the power of Ginger Oil and Turmeric,
Forever Active HA is your key to becoming a well-oiled machine again!
<ul>
 	<li>Lubricates the joints and moisturizes skin</li>
 	<li>Contains beneficial ginger and turmeric root for joint support</li>
 	<li>Hyaluronic acid (HA) is a key component of synovial uid and cartilage that
makes lubrication of joints and shock absorption possible.</li>
 	<li>Produced using a patented process, it provides low molecular weight HA
which the intestines can easily absorb.</li>
 	<li>Enhanced with Ginger Oil and Tumeric which have natural anti-in
ammatory, antioxidant and blood circulation improvement properties.</li>
</ul>
The FOREVER ACTIVE HA is not sold in any pharmacy shop. You can now
place your order direct from our website <a href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/active-ha/">here&gt;&gt;ORDER NOW&lt;&lt;</a>

&nbsp;

<strong>FOREVER ABSORBENT-C</strong>
<div id="image_1265625960" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502811721438absorbc600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Scientists and physicians have known for centuries that Vitamin C is an
essential nutrient and critical for healthy collage formation, but it is only
recently that scientists have uncovered that Vitamin C plays a role in nearly every step of collagen formation. Vitamin C is often depleted by stress high
levels of physical activity and certain medications. It’s important to get enough
Vitamin C on a daily basis to help support healthy joints.
<ul>
 	<li>Contains vitamin C plus citrus bio avonoids in a bran base for time release
effect.</li>
 	<li>Provides building block for collagen, a naturally occurring protein that
contributes tensile strength to ligaments, cartilage, skin and bones.</li>
 	<li>Helps to repair soft bone tissue and synovial membrane.</li>
</ul>
The FOREVER ABSORBENT-C is not sold in any pharmacy shop. You can now
place your order direct from our website <a href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/absorbent-c/">here&gt;&gt;ORDER NOW&lt;&lt;</a>

&nbsp;

<strong>ALOE MSM GEL</strong>
<div id="image_1165768261" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated.png" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated.png 900w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated-768x768.png 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated-600x600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190913288Aloe-MSM-Gel-Isolated-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="800" height="800" /></div>
</div>
When you’re looking for soothing relief, reach for Aloe MSM Gel. MSM stands
for Methyl Sulfonyl Methane, an organic sulfur found in almost all living
organisms. In fact, sulfur is the third most abundant substance in our body.

The other main ingredient in Aloe MSM Gel is pure, stabilized Aloe Vera. Aloe
MSM Gel combines these two powerful ingredients with herbal extracts and
other select ingredients for soothing relief anytime.
<ul>
 	<li>A special formulation of MSM and herbal extracts in a 100% stabilized Aloe
Vera base that helps reduce inflammation through clearing up clogged cell
membranes.</li>
 	<li>Used together with ALOE HEAT LOTION for best results.</li>
</ul>
The Aloe MSM Gel is not sold in any pharmacy shop. You can now
place your order direct from our website <a href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/aloe-msm-gel/">here&gt;&gt;ORDER NOW&lt;&lt;</a>

&nbsp;

<strong>ALOE HEAT LOTION</strong>
<div id="image_313626114" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated.png" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated.png 900w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated-768x768.png 768w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated-600x600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1440190885952Aloe-Heat-Lotion-Isolated-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="800" height="800" /></div>
</div>
<ul>
 	<li>Herbal remedy for fast relief of aching joints and sore muscles through
improving blood circulation.</li>
 	<li>It employs the power of eucalyptus, enhanced with 100% stabilized Aloe
Vera for deep penetration to give faster results.</li>
</ul>
The ALOE HEAT LOTION is not sold in any pharmacy shop. You can now
place your order direct from our website <a href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/aloe-heat-lotion/">here&gt;&gt;ORDER NOW&lt;&lt;</a></div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="4dde8c5" class="elementor-element elementor-element-4dde8c5 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="5f2435a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-5f2435a elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="4d60638" class="elementor-element elementor-element-4d60638 animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/">Forever Arthritis Care Pack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/forever-arthritis-care-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>HORMONE BOOSTER PACK</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1200</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Hormone imbalance is at the root of many common ailments, from skin conditions like acne, Infertility, psoriasis and eczema to digestive issues like leaky gut and bloating to sleep problems, like insomnia and lack of energy. Hormone Reset Fertility Kit will Help you heal your hormones – for good. The Hormone Booster Kit contains herbs &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">HORMONE BOOSTER PACK</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/">HORMONE BOOSTER PACK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1200" class="elementor elementor-1200" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="678e05a4" class="elementor-element elementor-element-678e05a4 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="1232c131" class="elementor-element elementor-element-1232c131 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="5aec7236" class="elementor-element elementor-element-5aec7236 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Hormone imbalance is at the root of many common ailments, from skin conditions like
acne, Infertility, psoriasis and eczema to digestive issues like leaky gut and bloating to
sleep problems, like insomnia and lack of energy. Hormone Reset Fertility Kit will Help
you heal your hormones – for good.

The Hormone Booster Kit contains herbs and supplements to support the body in
promoting healthy hormonal balance, a healthy uterine lining, regular ovulation,
improved estrogen metabolism, improved quick recovery from ill health, Helps reset
hormone and improved digestion. For optimal hormonal balance.

<strong>You Need Hormone Booster if:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>You’re consistently lacking energy</li>
 	<li>You have trouble falling or staying asleep</li>
 	<li>You suffer from bloating</li>
 	<li>Your libido is low</li>
 	<li>You’ve been diagnosed with hormone imbalances</li>
 	<li>You’re plagued by constant bloating</li>
 	<li>You suffer from anxiety, depression or mood swings</li>
 	<li>You have acne, eczema, psoriasis, or other skin conditions</li>
 	<li>You have trouble losing unwanted weight, even when you’re eating well and
exercising regularly</li>
 	<li>Your blood sugar dips and rockets throughout the day</li>
 	<li>You’ve suspected something is wrong with your hormones, from your thyroid to
your adrenals to your cortisol levels, but been unsure exactly what it was or how to
fix it</li>
 	<li>You believe in treating underlying whole body issues, not single-symptom pills
designed for specific symptoms</li>
</ul>
With powerful supplements include in Hormone Booster Kit is everything you need to
make imbalanced hormones a thing of the past. Imagine having clear, glowing skin;
uninterrupted, restorative slumber; and digestion that’s efficient and nourishing to
your body.

<strong>Benefits of the Hormone Booster:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Supports the body’s natural ability to remove excess estrogen from the body
(unopposed estrogen fuels hormonal imbalance)*</li>
 	<li>Enhance strong immune system and promote over-all body functions at its optimal
healthy level.</li>
 	<li>Speed up healing and increase the effective of herbal treatment by 300%.
It Helps improve digestion and healthy weight.</li>
 	<li>Clear up many health complaints and make body less prone to illness.</li>
 	<li>Prevent health crisis before they occur and gives benefits beyond fertility and
wellness.</li>
 	<li>Encourages woman Cycle Regularity</li>
 	<li>Helps Woman Body Ovulate Regularly</li>
 	<li>Become more relaxed and enjoy excellent sleep</li>
 	<li>Eliminate most digestive disorders</li>
 	<li>Feel lighter, healthier, look younger and more energetic.</li>
 	<li>Aids the body in the formation of a healthy uterine lining through key whole food
nutrients and herbs*</li>
 	<li>Encourages ovulation through traditionally used herbs*</li>
 	<li>Encourages normal circulation, helping to bring fresh blood and oxygen to the
reproductive system*</li>
 	<li>Promotes healthy digestion and a reduction in cravings for sweets to help support
the body in maintaining healthy blood sugar levels*</li>
</ul>
<strong>Hormone Booster</strong> contains: – Forever ImmuBlend, ARGI+®, Aloe vera Gel, Multi-
Maca, Forever Daily, Forever Bee pollen

<strong>Forever ImmuBlend</strong>
<div id="image_1130597644" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502881899779immublend600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Forever ImmuBlend is designed to support immune system function by addressing all
aspects of the immune system from its 􀃗rst line of defence to its last. Each ingredient
in our proprietary blend is speci􀃗cally chosen for the crucial role it plays in supporting
your bodys immune system function. It helps the bodys biological defence system to
operate at peak performance so you can carry on your daily routine without any cares.

<strong>ARGI+® (L-Arginine,Miracle Molecule)</strong>
<div id="image_1646108280" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484840434019ARGI600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
<strong>L-Arginine</strong> is an amino acid that’s so potent, scientists refer to it as the “Miracle
Molecule.” And for good reason, because our bodies convert L-Arginine into nitric
oxide, a molecule that helps blood vessels relax and open wide for greater blood 􀃘ow.
Greater blood flow supports many important functions in our body:

<strong>Benefits of L-Arginine</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Healthy blood pressure levels</li>
 	<li>Overall cardiovascular health</li>
 	<li>Immune function</li>
 	<li>Muscle growth</li>
 	<li>Bone &amp; tissue growth &amp; repair</li>
 	<li>Male sexual function</li>
 	<li>Fat and glucose metabolism</li>
 	<li>Anti-aging hormone production and more</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Aloe vera Gel</strong></h3>
<div id="image_1204659389" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_.jpg 512w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-150x150.jpg 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-300x300.jpg 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/cropped-41CXrYv77HL._SY355_-100x100.jpg 100w" alt="" width="512" height="512" /></div>
</div>
It detoxifies the entire body systems of toxins.It contains more than 200 nutritional compounds.This is
a general body tonic that replenishes lost vital nutrients.

Aloe Vera gel is also one of the best body cleansers. It cleanses toxic matter from the
stomach, kidneys, spleen, bladder, liver, and is the most effective colon cleanser.

Contains amino acids that are essential for good health. Aloe Vera Gel is great for
healthy digestion and helps improve nutrient absorption.

<strong>Multi-Maca</strong>
<div id="image_1186025199" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895507371multimaca600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895507371multimaca600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895507371multimaca600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895507371multimaca600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502895507371multimaca600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
is known as the Sex Herb of Incas. It increases fertility in
both male and female and helps to regulate the hormones. It increases the
Spermatozoid count and its mobility. It improves Libido and Virility.

Maca is a great help in balancing hormonal status, symptoms of menopause, hot
flashes, prevention and aid in the treatment of osteoporosis, irregular periods,
problems related to PMS, primenopauzu, stimulating fertility (drink to conception,
discontinued during pregnancy and during breastfeeding.better athletic performance
and sexual stimulation – an aphrodisiac.

Maca has proven to be extremely helpful in regulating hormonal status (amount of
testosterone), increase energy and endurance, for better athletic performance, build
muscle mass (bodibilden), symptoms of andropause (male menopause), impotence,
problems with erection and ejaculation, stimulating fertility

Used for: pain relief nervous origin, better circulation, fatigue, impotence, sexual
weakness, frigidity, distress, anxiety, neurosteniju, bad memory (forgetfulness),
insomnia, hypochondria, a natural antibiotic with antiviral properties.

<strong>Forever Daily</strong>
<div id="image_1014501093" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1484826179011daily600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
Provides essential vitamins and minerals and helps to ensure we are
obtaining the levels of these nutrients we need for optimal health. It can also help to fill
in the nutrient gaps that can result from our modern diets. These nutrients are then
carried along the Nutrient Superhighway to our cells and tissues to support optimal
functioning.

<strong>Forever Bee pollen</strong>
<div id="image_1505311886" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1497273403290POLLEN600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
contains more nutrients per calorie than any other nutritional
supplement and so it is little wonder that it is cited as one of the most complete foods
available. In fact, the human body could survive on bee pollen alone, with just the
addition of fibre and water.

The nutrients in bee pollen are readily digestible and easily absorbed by the human
body. Many people obtain benefit, including athletes who take it for stamina and
energy and to help them maintain good health.

Because bee pollen varies from source to source depending on time of year, location,
ect. it is hard to pinpoint exact nutritional bene􀃗ts as they may be different with each
batch. Bee pollen does contain vitamins, minerals, antioxidants, proteins and amino
acids. It is said that bee pollen contains antihistamine properties which may reduce
allergies.

Bee pollen has been reported to have great results in boosting immunity, fertility for
both men and women, reducing allergies and boosting overall nutrition, as well as
having healing benefits for a variety of other health conditions.

In addition, <strong>Forever Bee Pollen</strong> has a number of specific benefits:
<ul>
 	<li>Multi-vitamin and multi-mineral supplement</li>
 	<li>Energy booster</li>
 	<li>Aids digestion</li>
 	<li>Contains many trace elements including vitamins, minerals and amino acids</li>
 	<li>The rich cocktail of nutrients in bee pollen can help to correct body chemistry and
so counteract the effects of food additives and preservatives.</li>
 	<li>It is a naturally high source of zinc and vitamin B6, making it extremely bene􀃗cial.</li>
 	<li>It can desensitise the body, making it a good supplement.</li>
 	<li>It is also ‘bacteriostatic’ – suppressing the activity of bacteria and increases the
effective elimination of wastes and poisons from the body.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Aloe Blossom Herbal Tea </strong></h3>
<div id="image_1859720211" class="img has-hover x md-x lg-x y md-y lg-y">
<div class="img-inner dark"><img class="attachment-large size-large" src="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502793690210tea600.png" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502793690210tea600.png 600w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502793690210tea600-150x150.png 150w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502793690210tea600-300x300.png 300w, https://aloevera.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/1502793690210tea600-100x100.png 100w" alt="" width="600" height="600" /></div>
</div>
When we are stressed out or feeling down, it’s amazing
what a cup of tea can do. Aloe Blossom Herbal Tea, seasoned with the right touch of
Aloe Blossoms, and other finest herbs gives a warm, fruity flavor with ginger and zesty
orange peel for a soothing and refreshing feeling.

A cup before bedtime relaxes a stressed mind and body and promotes sleep. Naturally
low calorie &amp; no caffeine makes it an ideal fit for a nutritional life style that is essential
for healthy living. Along with exercise and healthy diet, <strong>Aloe Blossom Herbal Tea</strong>
makes a great companion tool for our weight management program.
Order your <strong>Hormone Booster Today.</strong></div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="5445b43" class="elementor-element elementor-element-5445b43 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="afbb2dd" class="elementor-element elementor-element-afbb2dd elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="2090c61" class="elementor-element elementor-element-2090c61 animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/">HORMONE BOOSTER PACK</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/hormone-booster-pack/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bones Care</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 14:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1195</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Broken bones occur by accident or because the bones have some de􀃗ciency such as a lack of Vitamin D and Calcium. They may also occur owing to Osteoporosis. Symptoms: Deformity of the extremities Obstruction of the normal movement of limbs, Pain, Sensation of rubbing between 2 bones. Causes: Accidents Lack of Calcium Lack of Vitamin &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Bones Care</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/">Bones Care</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1195" class="elementor elementor-1195" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="6d656e25" class="elementor-element elementor-element-6d656e25 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="43ac902f" class="elementor-element elementor-element-43ac902f elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="7e8fc363" class="elementor-element elementor-element-7e8fc363 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">Broken bones occur by accident or because the bones have some de􀃗ciency such as a
lack of Vitamin D and Calcium. They may also occur owing to Osteoporosis.

<strong>Symptoms:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Deformity of the extremities</li>
 	<li>Obstruction of the normal movement of limbs,
Pain,</li>
 	<li>Sensation of rubbing between 2 bones.</li>
</ul>
<strong>Causes:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Accidents</li>
 	<li>Lack of Calcium</li>
 	<li>Lack of Vitamin D</li>
 	<li>Osteoporosis</li>
</ul>
<strong>Suggested Treatment:</strong>
<ol>
 	<li>Immoblise person (lay person down) and place affected area in a splint.</li>
 	<li>Get a competent person to set the bones straight so that they can mend correctly.</li>
 	<li>During recovery, it is necessary that new tissue be formed to join the broken bones
together and the damaged tissue be repaired; therefore the recommended under
Products is required.</li>
 	<li>Stop eating refined carbohydrates such as sugar (candy), since these elimiinate
calcium.</li>
</ol>
<strong>Products:</strong>

<strong>Nature-Min Tablets.</strong> 6 tablets daily, 2 with each meal. Needed for proper composition
of bones.

<strong>Calcium Tablets</strong> (with Vitamin D and Magnesium). 6 tablets daily, 2 with each meal.
Essential for bone growth and reparation.

<strong>Absorbent-C Tablets.</strong> 3 tablets daily, 1 with each meal. Powerful anti-oxidant, repairs
and maintains body tissue.

<strong>Nutritional Shake.</strong> 1 daily. Excellent source of a balanced meal, providing amino acids,
proteins, fiber, vitamins and minerals.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="e46cf92" class="elementor-element elementor-element-e46cf92 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="b5e0a16" class="elementor-element elementor-element-b5e0a16 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="cff6c8c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-cff6c8c animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/">Bones Care</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bones-care/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>BLEEDING GUMS</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 14:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1185</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Buy Bleeding Gums Pack and get 1 Free Extra Toothgel When people don’t practice proper dental hygiene, bacteria in the mouth forms plaque on the teeth. These bacteria may cause your gums to become in􀃘amed, which results in red, swollen, or bleeding gums. For many people with gingivitis, this in􀃘ammation is not painful. … gums &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">BLEEDING GUMS</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/">BLEEDING GUMS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1185" class="elementor elementor-1185" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="467d095" class="elementor-element elementor-element-467d095 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="a18f32f" class="elementor-element elementor-element-a18f32f elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="618984a" class="elementor-element elementor-element-618984a animated zoomIn animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;zoomIn&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix"><p><img class="aligncenter" src="https://media.giphy.com/media/zNaC251b9m9zy/giphy.gif" alt="Image result for Offer Gif" /></p></div>
				</div>
				</div>
				<div data-id="b66b81c" class="elementor-element elementor-element-b66b81c animated zoomIn animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-heading" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;zoomIn&quot;}" data-element_type="heading.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
			<h2 class="elementor-heading-title elementor-size-default">Buy Bleeding Gums Pack and get 1 Free Extra Toothgel</h2>		</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="37a12b1" class="elementor-element elementor-element-37a12b1 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="29cc7d66" class="elementor-element elementor-element-29cc7d66 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="3dff62f5" class="elementor-element elementor-element-3dff62f5 animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">When people don’t practice proper dental hygiene, bacteria in the mouth forms plaque
on the teeth. These bacteria may cause your gums to become in􀃘amed, which results
in red, swollen, or bleeding gums. For many people with gingivitis, this in􀃘ammation is
not painful. … gums that bleed during and after toothbrushing.

<strong>Symptoms:</strong>

A frequent problem known as periodontitis or gingivitis causes swelling of the gums.
Pyorrhea can result, characterised by strong in􀃘ammation and pus, resulting in tooth
loss.

<strong>Causes</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Food and bacteria caught between gums and teeth.</li>
 	<li>Smoking</li>
 	<li>Breathing through the mouth and lack of oral hygiene.</li>
</ul>
<strong>Suggested Treatment:</strong>
<ul>
 	<li>Apply Aloe Vera Activator Extract to the gums to reduce gingivitis.</li>
 	<li>Brush teeth daily with Aloe Vera &amp; Propolis toothpaste.</li>
 	<li>Massage gums.</li>
</ul>
<strong>Hormone Booster</strong> contains: – Forever ImmuBlend, ARGI+®, Aloe vera Gel, Multi-
Maca, Forever Daily, Forever Bee pollen

<strong>Products</strong>

<strong>Aloe Vera &amp; Propolis Toothgel.</strong> At least 3 times daily. Is anti-in􀃘ammatory, pain
inhibitor, natural anti-biotic.

<strong>Aloe Vera Activator Extract.</strong> Do the following twice after brushing one’s teeth – rub
the gums with a brush containing a few drops. Rinse the mouth with the extract,
keeping the liquid in the mouth for at least half a minute.

<strong>Absorbent-C Tablets –</strong> 6 tablets daily, 2 with each meal. Powerful anti-oxidant.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="4fdcba3" class="elementor-element elementor-element-4fdcba3 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="5c79ae7" class="elementor-element elementor-element-5c79ae7 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="3b1f352" class="elementor-element elementor-element-3b1f352 animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/">BLEEDING GUMS</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/bleeding-gums/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kidney Detox Kit</title>
		<link>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/</link>
		<comments>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[smartikastore]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/?post_type=product&#038;p=1180</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The Kidney Detox Kit is designed to detoxify, flush and purge the kidneys of built up toxins. Toxins accumulate and stones form when the kidneys aren’t functioning at normal efficiency. A Kidney Detox involves eating a healthy organic diet and drinking an organic, herbal kidney cleanse supplement for 2 to 3 weeks to stimulate the &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Kidney Detox Kit</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/">Kidney Detox Kit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[		<div data-elementor-type="post" data-elementor-id="1180" class="elementor elementor-1180" data-elementor-settings="[]">
			<div class="elementor-inner">
				<div class="elementor-section-wrap">
							<section data-id="64a25f68" class="elementor-element elementor-element-64a25f68 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="4b1ef542" class="elementor-element elementor-element-4b1ef542 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="393abc3b" class="elementor-element elementor-element-393abc3b animated fadeInUp animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInUp&quot;}" data-element_type="text-editor.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-text-editor elementor-clearfix">The Kidney Detox Kit is designed to detoxify, flush and purge the kidneys of built up
toxins. Toxins accumulate and stones form when the kidneys aren’t functioning at normal efficiency. A Kidney Detox involves eating a healthy organic diet and drinking an organic, herbal kidney cleanse supplement for 2 to 3 weeks to stimulate the kidneys and soften any deposits. The Kidney Detox protocol also includes an intestinal cleanse
with probiotic supplement which helps encourage a balanced internal environment to enable proper nutrient absorption.
<h3><strong>The Top 4 Reasons You Need a Kidney Cleanse</strong></h3>
<ol>
 	<li><strong>Supports Whole Body Detoxification &#8211; </strong>Each system in your body requires special attention. Just as the importance of liver cleansing is well known, kidney cleansing is mandatory for enhancing total body cleansing.</li>
 	<li><strong>Promotes Normal Kidney Function &#8211; </strong>The primary responsibilities of the kidneys are to 􀃗lter impurities from your body. Ifthey’re not performing at normal efficiency, a buildup of toxins may result..</li>
 	<li><strong>Detoxifies the Kidneys and Intestines &#8211; </strong>Your body’s waste management system has multiple departments. Nectar is effective at flushing impurities from the kidneys, Probiotic facilitates detoxification of the intestines and colon.</li>
 	<li><strong>Boosts Your Well Being &#8211; </strong>When you’re functioning normally on the inside, you feel great on the outside. Internal cleansing is one of the most effective measures for boosting your energy levels and making you feel better.</li>
</ol>
&nbsp;

When you’re functioning normally on the inside, you feel great on the outside. Internal
cleansing is one of the most effective measures for boosting your energy levels and
making you feel better.

<span style="font-size: 120%;"><strong>Health Benefits of a Kidney Detox</strong></span>
<ul>
 	<li>Nutritional support helps the kidneys break down and eliminate toxins.</li>
 	<li>Flushes excess uric acid, cleans the urinary tract.</li>
 	<li>Promotes regular fluid balance to release water retention.</li>
 	<li>Aloe gel uses the gentle power to detox the intestines and colon.</li>
 	<li>Probiotic encourages the healthy intestinal flora that enhance digestion.</li>
 	<li>Increases energy and vitality to encourage overall health.</li>
</ul>
<span style="font-size: 120%;"><strong>Learn about the Top 3 Questions People ask about Kidney</strong></span>
<span style="font-size: 120%;"><strong>Cleansing</strong></span>
<ol>
 	<li>What can I expect? A kidney cleanse may flush deposits and toxins from your
kidneys, bladder, and urinary tract. Because the Kidney Cleanse Kit includes Oxy-
Powder, you can also expect to purge other toxic material trapped in the kidneys and
intestines so they may also exit your body.</li>
 	<li>Is the kidney cleanse safe? The Kidney Cleanse Kit is very safe and should not cause
harm. Everyone is different, however, and some persons have reported experiencing a
healing crisis. This is normal! Fatigue or headache are temporary and indicative of
toxin movement.</li>
 	<li>How long will it take to cleanse my kidneys? This depends on your current status.
Many people have never cleansed their kidneys and have an accumulation of toxins.
One cleanse may not be enough and performing three kidney cleanses a year is
recommended. The best results are reported by people who have performed three
cleanses in a row with a 5 day break between each.</li>
</ol>
<span style="font-size: 120%;"><strong>Suggested Products for Kidneys Detox.</strong></span>

The Below herbal remedies have multiple functions, and together form an important
part of supplements to enhance and protect the vital kidney energy system.

<strong>Aloe Vera Gel (juice). 120ml –</strong> 180ml mixed with orange or grape juice through out the
day.

<strong>Ginkgo Plus Tablets.</strong> 3 tablets daily, 1 with each meal. Contains Schizandra Chinesis
which enhances the kidney and liver functions.

<strong>Lycium PlusTablets.</strong> 3 tablets daily, 1 with each meal. Contains licorice extract which
improves the liver functions and reducing the amount of toxic enzymes in the blood.

<strong>Absorbent-C Tablets.</strong> 2 to 3 tablets a day, 1 with each meal. Powerful anti-oxidant,
prevents oxidation in cells and strengthens immune system.

<strong>Garlic &amp; Thyme Softgels.</strong> 3 capsules a day, 1 with each meal. Very strong antiin
inflammatory.

<strong>Field of Greens Tablets</strong> 2 to 3 tablets a day, 1 with each meal. Fields of Greens
provide the minerals, proteins, amino acids, enzymes, anti-oxidants and chlorophyll
you need. Besides, this product contains barley grass, wheat grass and alfalfa which are
all alkaline ingredients to balance blood’s pH level.</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
				<section data-id="712d160" class="elementor-element elementor-element-712d160 elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default elementor-section elementor-top-section" data-element_type="section">
						<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
				<div class="elementor-row">
				<div data-id="0e3db59" class="elementor-element elementor-element-0e3db59 elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column" data-element_type="column">
			<div class="elementor-column-wrap  elementor-element-populated">
					<div class="elementor-widget-wrap">
				<div data-id="1b7fed0" class="elementor-element elementor-element-1b7fed0 animated fadeInLeft animated-slow elementor-invisible elementor-widget elementor-widget-image" data-settings="{&quot;_animation&quot;:&quot;fadeInLeft&quot;}" data-element_type="image.default">
				<div class="elementor-widget-container">
					<div class="elementor-image">
										<img width="1024" height="341" src="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg" class="attachment-large size-large" alt="" srcset="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-1024x341.jpg 1024w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-300x100.jpg 300w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-768x256.jpg 768w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original-600x200.jpg 600w, https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/wp-content/uploads/2018/07/newproject_1_original.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" />											</div>
				</div>
				</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
						</div>
			</div>
		</section>
						</div>
			</div>
		</div>
		<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/">Kidney Detox Kit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke">Smartika Shop</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>https://smartikaecommerce.aloeveraforkenya.co.ke/product/kidney-detox-kit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
